Finding Aid for Democratic Party of Michigan records, 1932-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Headquarters (Lansing) files 1951-1982
  - 1977
    - Chairperson: Morley Winograd
      - Correspondence
        - Michigan House of Representatives (Box 64)
        - Other State Chairmen (Box 64)
      - Democratic National Committee: Winograd Commission (correspondence and reports) (Box 64)
    - Conventions and Conferences
      - Democratic Midwest Conference (Box 64)
      - Democratic National Midterm Conference: 1978
        - Amendments to Call (Box 64)
        - Site Selection (Box 64)
      - State Spring Convention
        - General (Box 64)
        - Resolutions Committee (Box 64)
    - Committees, Councils, and Commissions
      - Economic Advisory Council (Box 64)
      - Policy Committee, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Damman, James (Box 64)
      (correspondence with Morley Winograd)
    - Democratic National Committee (membership) (Box 64)
    - FAIR Plan (Committee to Reform Judicial Campaign Financing): includes previous and later material (Box 64)
    - Field Staff Representative: Sue Jones (mostly correspondence) (Box 64)
    - Fundraising
      - General (mostly correspondence re: Century and 500 Clubs) (Box 64)
      - Jeff/Jack, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Hart, Peter D., Research Associates (Box 64)
    - Industrial Counties Seminar (Box 64)
    - Issues: Public and legislative
      - Crime (Box 64)
      - Friend of the Court Reform (Box 64)
      - Judges-Appointment vs Election (Box 64)
        (includes previous and later material)
      - Political Reform Law (P.A. 388) (Box 64)
    - Marshall, William C. (President-Michigan State AFL-CIO): Remarks Before the Michigan Republican Leadership Conference (Box 64)
    - Meetings
      - D.S.C.C. (Box 64)
      - D.S.C.C. Officers (Box 64)
    - Membership: D.S.C.C. (Box 64)
    - Michigan Women's Commission (Box 64)
    - Operating Expenses: D.S.C.C. (Box 64)
    - Party Membership (Box 64)
    - Personnel Practices: D.S.C.C. (Box 64)
    - PIRGIM (Box 64)
    - Vice-Chairperson: Olivia Maynard
      - Correspondence: General (includes undated) (Box 64)
      - Democratic National Committee Related Material: includes correspondence, minutes (Box 64)
    - Women's Caucus (Box 64)
    - Women's Organizations at the County Level: responses to Maynard questionnaire (Box 64)
  - 1978
    - Agriculture: U.S.D.A. report to Olivia Maynard re: Farmers Home Administration loan and grant program in Michigan 1977 (Box 65)
    - Approval Voting (Box 65)
    - Campaigns and Elections
      - General (Box 65)
      - Ballot Proposals-Tax Limitation (Box 65)
      - Campaign Contributions (mostly correspondence) (Box 65)
      - Campaign Finance Reporting, 2 folders (Box 65)
      - Campaign Plan (Box 65)
      - Candidate Debates (Box 65)
      - Candidate Training Session (Box 65)
      - Candidates' Meeting January 10, 1978 (Box 65)
      - Election Analysis (Flint Journal clipping November 12, 1978 (Box 65)
      - Election Results ("Unofficial Totals) November 9, 1978" (Box 65)
      - Federal Election Campaign Act (Box 65)
        (Morley Winograd handwritten memo to District Chairs and Treasurers)
      - Get Out The Vote Plan
        - General, 7 folders (Box 65)
        - Genesee County (Box 65)
        - Macomb County (Box 65)
        - Phone Banks (Box 65)
      - Gubernatorial Race
        - General, 2 folders (Box 65)
        - Potential Gubernatorial Candidates (Box 65)
      - House Campaign Coordinating Committee (includes later material) (Box 66)
      - Legislative Campaign Coordinating Committee (Box 66)
      - Precinct Delegates (Box 66)
      - Primary: Gubernatorial and Senatorial Party Guidelines (Box 66)
      - State
        - Educational Posts (Box 66)
        - House Races (Box 66)
          (includes responses to candidate interview questionnaire)
        - Senate Races, 2 folders (Box 66)
        - Supreme Court Candidates (Box 66)
      - United States
        - Congressional Races, 2 folders (Box 66)
        - Senate Races, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Chairperson: Morley Winograd
      - Association of State Chairmen
        - General (Box 66)
        - Memphis Meeting (Box 66)
      - Correspondence
        - General (Box 66)
        - Democratic National Committee (Box 66)
        - Market Opinion Research (Box 66)
        - Michigan House of Representatives (Box 66)
        - Other State Chairmen (Box 66)
        - Staff Memos (mostly meeting announcements) (Box 66)
      - Democratic National Committee
        - General (Box 66)
        - Administration Policies on the Mid-East (Box 66)
        - Executive Committee meeting March 16, 1978 (Box 66)
        - Meetings
          - January 1978 (Box 66)
          - June 9-10, 1978 (Box 66)
        - Rules and by-Laws Committee (Box 66)
        - Winograd Commission (Box 66)
      - UAW Meeting (Box 66)
        (controversy re: appointment of Willa Mae King to Public Service Commission, and Winograd Commission report)
    - Committees, Councils, and Commissions
      - Economic Advisory Council, 2 folders (Box 66)
      - Legislative Coordinating Committee, 3 folders (Box 67)
      - Policy Committee, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Conventions and Conferences
      - Democratic National Mid-Term Conference
        (see also Vice-Chairperson)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 67)
        - Arrangements, Invitations (Box 67)
        - Challenges Committee (Box 67)
        - Delegation Selection (general) (Box 67)
        - Michigan Delegation
          - General (Box 67)
          - Certification (Box 67)
          - Selection Process, 3 folders (Box 67)
        - Panel Discussions (Box 67)
        - Program and Agenda Committee (Olivia Maynard-member) (Box 67)
        - Resolutions (Box 67)
      - State Fall Convention
        - General, 2 folders (Box 67)
        - Fundraiser (Box 67)
        - Platform Committee, 2 folders (Box 67)
        - Rules Committee (Box 67)
    - Field Representative: Sue Jones: Correspondence (letter re: grant under Older American Act) (Box 67)
    - Fundraising
      - Century Club (correspondence) (Box 67)
      - Jeff/Jack, 4 folders (Box 68)
      - Personal Contributions (correspondence) (Box 68)
    - Griffin, Robert: Voting Record Analysis (Box 68)
    - Hart, Peter D., Research Associates (Box 68)
    - Issues: Public and Legislative
      - Crime (Box 68)
      - Domestic Violence (Box 68)
        (includes outside studies and reports)
      - Lobby Reform bill
        - General (Box 68)
        - Drafts, 2 folders (Box 68)
      - PBB (Box 68)
      - "Public Issues in Michigan" (House Democratic Research Staff) (Box 68)
      - "Legislative Issues-- 1975-1978" and "Ballot Proposals--1978" (Senate Democratic Office) (Box 68)
    - Jewish Precincts (Box 68)
    - Lafayette Avenue: 1300 (Box 68)
      (materials re: D.S.C.C. office occupancy)
    - Meetings
      - D.S.C.C. (Box 68)
      - Leadership (Box 68)
    - Michigan Congressmen (Box 68)
      (includes endorsement of House resolution to expel Monte Geralds)
    - Michigan Republican National State Elections Committee (Campaign Finance Reports) (Box 68)
    - Milliken, William (includes "Job Performance" reports) (Box 68)
    - Official County/District Organizations (per Public Act 388) (Box 68)
    - Operating Budget: D.S.C.C. (Box 68)
    - Operating Statements (Box 68)
    - Party Membership (Box 68)
    - Party Platform (Box 68)
      (includes "1978 Recommended Platform" and draft)
    - Political Action Committees (Box 68)
    - Polls- Detroit News (Box 68)
      (includes copies of Don Riegle's correspondence re: Market Opinion Research conflict of interest)
    - Vice-Chairperson: Olivia Maynard
      - Correspondence: General (Box 68)
      - Democratic National Midterm Conference (Box 68)
        (includes Morley Winograd testimony on Michigan Primary)
      - Fundraising: Jeff/Jack (Box 69)
    - Women's Caucus (Box 69)
  - 1979
    - Approval Voting (Box 69)
      (mostly correspondence between Morley Winograd and Steven Brams)
    - Campaigns and Elections
      - Campaign Finance Reporting
        - General (Box 69)
        - Rulings by Attorney General (Box 69)
      - Campaign Financing: Gubernatorial (Box 69)
      - Campaign Strategy Meetings (Box 69)
      - City of Detroit Election Project (Box 69)
      - County and Township Election Strategy Sessions (Box 69)
    - Census: 1980 (Box 69)
    - Chairperson: Morley Winograd January 1, 1979-October 13, 1979
      - Association of State Democratic Chairs (Box 69)
      - Correspondence
        - General (includes inter-office memos) (Box 69)
        - AFL-CIO (Box 69)
        - Democratic National Committee (Box 69)
        - Michigan House of Representatives (Box 69)
        - Other State Chairmen (Box 69)
        - Staff Memos (Box 69)
      - Democratic National Committee
        - Compliance Review Commission (Box 69)
    - Chairperson: Olivia Maynard, beginning October 13, 1979
      - Correspondence
        - General (includes undated) (Box 69)
        - AFL-CIO (Box 69)
        - Democratic National Committee (Box 69)
        - Michigan House of Representatives (Box 69)
        - Other State Chairs (Box 69)
        - Staff Memos (Box 69)
      - Democratic National Committee Meeting November 7-9, 1979 (Box 69)
    - Committees, Councils, and Commissions
      - Economic Advisory Council (mostly Spring Symposium material) (Box 69)
      - Finance Committee (Box 69)
      - Legislative Coordinating Committee, 4 folders (Box 69)
      - Policy Committee
        - General, 3 folders (Box 69)
        - Subcommittees (Box 70)
          - International Relations (Box 70)
          - Natural Resources and Energy, 2 folders (Box 70)
      - Rules and Political Reform Committee (includes undated and later material) (Box 70)
    - Conventions and Conferences
      - Midwest Regional Conference (Box 70)
      - Democratic National Convention: 1980 Site Selection (Box 70)
      - State Spring Convention
        - General, 2 folders (Box 70)
        - Resolutions
          - General (Box 70)
          - County (Box 70)
      - County Strategy Sessions (Box 70)
      - Democratic National Committee: Newsletters (Box 70)
      - District Court Appointments (Box 70)
      - Federal Judgeships: Western District (Box 70)
      - Field Representative: Sue Jones: Correspondence (Box 70)
        (includes letter as assistant to the chair)
      - Fundraising
        - General (Box 70)
        - Century Fund (correspondence) (Box 70)
        - Jeff/Jack, 2 folders (Box 70)
        - Meet the Michigan Majority (Box 70)
    - Issues: Public and Legislative
      - Conflict of Interest Legislation (Box 70)
      - Domestic Violence (Box 70)
      - Insurance Reform, 2 folders (Box 70)
      - Nuclear Energy (clippings) (Box 70)
      - Presidential Primary Legislation (Michigan Senate bill No. 540) (Box 70)
        (includes Morley Winograd testimony before Michigan Senate, and undated)
      - Public Utilities (Attorney General news release) (Box 70)
      - Tax Reform, 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Leadership Newsletter (Box 70)
    - Leadership Retreat (Box 70)
    - Leadership Retreat (cont.) (Box 71)
    - Meetings
      - D.S.C.C.
        - March 24, 1979 (Box 71)
        - May 12, 1979 (Box 71)
        - August 19, 1979 (Box 71)
        - October 13, 1979 (Box 71)
        - December 8, 1979 (Box 71)
      - Officers (Box 71)
    - Michigan Chamber of Commerce (news release re: UAW PAC's) (Box 71)
    - Michigan Citizens For Life (copy of letter to Milliken) (Box 71)
    - Michigan Democratic Party (clippings) (Box 71)
    - Michigan Department of State, Office of Hearing and Legislation, Compliance and Rules Division (Box 71)
      (correspondence re: complaint against 1978 Milliken campaign for an illegal contribution, and clippings)
    - Michigan House of Representatives (Box 71)
    - Michigan Legislature Nuclear Energy Joint Committee (Box 71)
    - Michigan Senate
      - General (Box 71)
      - Committee on Municipalities and Elections (Box 71)
    - Operating Budget: includes March 1979-July 1980 finance calendar (Box 71)
    - Overseas Democrat (Box 71)
      (includes first issue)
    - Party Accountability Task Force, 6 folders (Box 71)
    - Party Directory (Box 71)
    - Party Membership (Box 71)
    - Power, Phillip (speech on ERA) (Box 71)
    - Public Administration Appointments (Box 71)
    - Vice-Chairperson: Olivia Maynard
      - Correspondence
        - General (Box 71)
        - Democrat National Committee (Box 71)
      - Democratic National Committee
        - General (Box 71)
        - Meeting May 25, 1979 (Box 71)
        - Targeting Sessions (Box 71)
    - White House Conference on Libraries (Box 71)
    - Women's Caucus (Box 71)
  - 1980
    - Approval Voting (Box 71)
    - Campaigns and Elections
      - General, 2 folders (Box 71)
      - General, 1 folders (Box 72)
      - Campaign Articles (Box 72)
      - Campaign Contributions (Box 72)
      - Campaign Finance Reporting (Box 72)
      - Get Out The Vote, 6 folders (Box 72)
      - Poll Results: poll conducted on November 2, 1980 (Box 72)
      - Presidential
        - Anderson, John (Box 72)
          (mostly re: The attempt to have his name removed from the Michigan primary)
        - Brown, Jerry (Brown for President Committee) (Box 72)
        - Carter/Mondale Presidential Committee, 3 folders (Box 72)
        - Kennedy for President (Box 72)
        - LaRouche, Lyndon: Citizens for Lyndon LaRouche (Box 72)
        - Reagan for President Committee (Box 72)
      - Screening Committee (Box 72)
      - Screening Committee (Box 73)
      - Special Elections (Box 73)
      - Staff Summaries of 1980 Campaign (Box 73)
      - State
        - Education Boards Candidates, 2 folders (Box 73)
        - House Campaigns (Box 73)
        - Supreme Court Candidates (Box 73)
      - United States Congressional Campaigns (Box 73)
    - Census (Box 73)
    - Chairperson: Olivia Maynard
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - January-March 1980 (Box 73)
          - April-June 1980 (Box 73)
          - July-December 1980 (Box 73)
        - Democratic National Committee (Box 73)
        - Other State Chairs (Box 73)
        - Speaking Requests (Box 73)
        - Thank You's and Congratulations (Box 73)
      - Democratic National Committee
        - General (Box 73)
        - County Caucuses (Box 73)
        - Michigan Delegation
          - Delegate List (Box 73)
          - Delegate Voting Results on Convention Floor (roll call tally sheets) (Box 73)
          - Selection Process
            - General, 2 folders (Box 73)
            - General, 5 folders (Box 74)
            - Clippings (Box 74)
      - State Fall Convention (mostly resolutions) (Box 74)
    - Committees, Councils, and Commissions
      - Education Committee (Box 74)
      - Legislative Coordinating Committee (Box 74)
      - Policy Committee (includes undated) (Box 74)
    - Democratic National Committee-Services Agreement (Box 74)
    - Fundraising
      - General (letter to Neil Staebler re: outstate Century Fund reception) (Box 74)
      - Jeff/Jack (Box 74)
    - Issues: Public and Legislative: Presidential Primary (clippings) (Box 74)
      (See also Democratic National Convention, Michigan Delegation, Selection Process, Clippings)
    - Leadership Newsletter (Box 74)
    - Michigan Democratic Party (clippings) (Box 74)
    - "Michigan Democrats Speak Out on National Issues" (Box 74)
    - Michigan House of Representatives (Box 74)
    - Michigan State Senate (Box 74)
    - Party Platform (recommended) (Box 74)
    - Women's Caucus (Box 74)
  - 1981
    - Campaigns and Elections: Campaign Training Session December 5, 1981 (Box 74)
    - Chairperson: Olivia Maynard
      - Association of State Democratic Chairs (Box 74)
      - Correspondence
        - County/District Memos (Box 74)
        - Democratic National Committee (Box 74)
    - Committees, Councils and Commissions: Legislative Coordinating Committee, 3 folders (Box 74)
    - Democratic National Committee (Box 74)
    - Michigan Democratic Party (clippings); includes material on the Michigan primary (Box 74)
    - Campaigns and Elections: Jones, Ruth: Manuscript and Paper: "State Election Campaign Financing: 1980"; "State Public Financing and the State Parties" (Box 74)
    - Chairperson: Olivia Maynard: Correspondence (Box 74)
      (Democratic National Committee telegram; UAW speaking engagement)
    - Conventions and Conferences: Democratic National Midterm Conference (Box 74)
    - Democratic National Telethon (Box 74)
    - Issues: Public and Legislative: "Public Issues In Michigan" (House Democratic Research Staff) (Box 74)
  - 1981-1983 (includes some earlier and later materials)
    - Abortion 1981 (Box 75)
    - AFL-CIO 1983 (Box 75)
    - Albosta, Don undated (Box 75)
    - Apportionment resolution 1981 (Box 75)
    - Attorney General 1981 (Box 75)
    - Austin, Richard 1980-1985 (Box 75)
    - Calendar (staff activities) 1981-1983 (Box 75)
    - Calendar (State Central Committee) 1981-1984 (Box 75)
    - Campaign Practices Guidelines 1984 (Box 75)
    - Campaign for President
      - General 1984 (Box 75)
      - Glenn 1984 (Box 75)
      - LaRouche 1984 (Box 75)
      - Mondale 1984 (Box 75)
    - Canvassers 1979-1983 (Box 75)
    - Carr, Bob 1982-1985 (Box 75)
    - Caucus information 1984 (Box 75)
    - Chamber of Commerce 1981 (Box 75)
    - Commission on National Elections 1985 (Box 75)
    - Committees
      - Agriculture 1979-1983 (Box 75)
      - Appeals 1971-1981 (Box 75)
      - Finance 1981-1983 (Box 75)
      - Legislative concerns 1981 (Box 75)
      - Policy 1982-1983 (Box 75)
      - Rules and political reform 1983 (Box 75)
      - Screening 1984 (Box 75)
    - Community organizations
      - ACORN 1979-1982 (Box 75)
      - Miscellaneous 1978-1980 (Box 75)
      - North Central 7 1977-1979 (Box 75)
    - Compulink 1981-1982 (Box 75)
    - Computers 1982-1983 (Box 75)
    - County/district organizations (memos) 1978-1983 (Box 75)
    - Democratic Education Officials 1976-1981 (Box 75)
    - Democratic Governors Association 1983 (Box 75)
    - Democratic Party (other states) 1981-1983 (Box 75)
    - District Appeals
      - General 1981-1982 (Box 75)
      - 13th District 1983 (Box 75)
      - Challenges 1980 (Box 75)
    - Election analysis
      - General 1980 (Box 75)
      - Michigan House/Senate 1985 (Box 75)
    - Elections
      - Campaign Finance Act 1983, 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Campaign Finance Act reports 1981-1983 (Box 75)
      - Fair Campaign Practices 1981-1982 (Box 75)
      - Federal Election Campaign Act rules 1975, 1980 (Box 75)
      - Federal Election Commission 1976-1982 (Box 75)
      - Federal Election laws 1983 (Box 75)
      - HB 4378/4379 1983 (Box 75)
    - Essential insurance 1979-1980 (Box 75)
    - Feedback II and III 1982 (Box 75)
    - Finances (budgets) 1982-1985 (Box 75)
    - Finances (membership drive) 1982-1983 (Box 75)
    - Fundraising
      - Art House 1983 (Box 75)
      - Bingo 1976-1983, 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Century/500 Club 1985 (Box 75)
      - Jefferson/Jackson Day 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Meet the Michigan Majority 1983 (Box 75)
      - National Telethon 1983 (Box 75)
      - Washington D.C. 1983 (Box 75)
    - Hart-Kennedy House 1977, 1983, 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Hatch Act 1977 (Box 75)
    - Housing Authority (Michigan State) 1977 (Box 75)
    - Hertel, John 1983 (Box 75)
    - Holmes, David 1983 (Box 75)
    - Keeping Track 1981 (Box 75)
    - Leadership meeting minutes 1983-1984 (Box 75)
    - Leadership newsletters 1979-1981 (Box 75)
    - Leadership Speakers' Bureau 1981 (Box 75)
    - Legislation: Worker's Compensation 1981-1982 (Box 75)
    - Legislature 1983 (Box 75)
    - Leland Commission 1982 (Box 75)
    - Liquor Control Commission (Michigan) 1974-1979 (Box 75)
    - Litigation
      - Agerstrand v. Austin 1981-1982 (Box 75)
      - Ferency v. Austin 1980-1981 (Box 75)
      - Langdon v. Michigan Democratic Party 1980 (Box 75)
      - Michigan Chamber of Commerce v. Austin 1981-1984 (Box 75)
    - Lobby Reform rules 1979 (Box 75)
    - Lobby Network 1981 (Box 75)
    - Lobbyists 1974-1981 (Box 76)
    - Massoglia and Associates 1979-1982 (Box 76)
    - Members (DSCC) (Box 76)
    - Michigan Tax Information Council 1983 (Box 76)
    - Milliken, William G. 1974-1981 (Box 76)
    - Miscellaneous 1981-1982 (Box 76)
    - Negative advertising against Carr/Albosta 1983 (Box 76)
    - Officers meeting (minutes) 1983-1984 (Box 76)
    - Personnel 1981-1983 (Box 76)
    - Recalls
      - De Maso 1983 (Box 76)
      - Elections to fill vacancies 1984 (Box 76)
      - Evans 1983 (Box 76)
      - Kelly 1983 (Box 76)
      - Mastin 1983 (Box 76)
      - McCollough 1983-1984 (Box 76)
      - Parrott 1983-1984 (Box 76)
      - Serotkin 1983 (Box 76)
    - Secretary of State 1983 (Box 76)
    - Senate-Levin 1979-1983 (Box 76)
    - Senate-Riegle 1979-1982 (Box 76)
    - Senate-Senate Action 1983 (Box 76)
    - Targeting Systems, Inc. 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - 1984
    - Association of State Democratic Chairs
      - General (Box 76)
      - Voter turnout program (Box 76)
    - Campaign (Box 76)
    - Campaign budget (Box 76)
    - Campaigns (House) (Box 76)
    - Carr, Bob (Box 76)
    - Caucus (proposed rules) (Box 76)
    - Caucus forms (Box 76)
    - Caucus returns (Box 76)
    - Caucuses (Box 76)
    - Caucuses (Presidential preference) (Box 76)
    - Computer (Box 76)
    - Correspondence (mailed out), 4 folders (Box 76)
    - Correspondence (received) (Box 77)
    - County-wide Democratic elected officials (Box 77)
    - Database (Box 77)
    - Democratic Lawyers of Michigan (Box 77)
    - Democratic National Committee; Women's Task Force (Box 77)
    - Democratic National Convention (Box 77)
    - Democratic Party Accountability (Box 77)
    - Democratic Party charter and bylaws (Box 77)
    - District Convention (Box 77)
    - Election day information (Box 77)
    - Fairness coalition (Box 77)
    - Financial statements (Box 77)
    - Fundraisers (Box 77)
    - Get out the vote summary (Box 77)
    - Governor's Council (Box 77)
    - Jackson (Jesse) campaign (Box 77)
    - Jackson v. Michigan Democratic Party (Box 77)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day (Box 77)
    - LaRouche, Lyndon (Box 77)
    - LaRouche challenge (Box 77)
    - Leadership-party officers meeting (Box 77)
    - Levin, Carl (Box 77)
    - McGovern, George (Box 77)
    - McInerny, Gary (includes voter survey) (Box 77)
    - Meet the Michigan Majority (Box 77)
    - Membership letter (Box 77)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 77)
    - Mondale, Walter (Box 77)
    - Policy Committee (Box 77)
    - Press releases (Box 77)
    - Proportional voting (Box 77)
    - Radio and television (Box 77)
    - Reapportionment (Box 77)
    - Recalls (Box 77)
    - Republican Campaign Committee (National) (Box 77)
    - Sachs, Ted (Box 77)
    - Sanford, Terry (Box 77)
    - Senate Minority (Box 77)
    - Shafer, Ann (Box 77)
    - State House races (Box 77)
    - State Legislative Races (radio spots) (Box 77)
    - State Representative Districts (Box 77)
    - Stewart, Tom (Box 77)
    - Twelfth District (Box 77)
    - Voter Opinion Research (Box 77)
    - Voter Registration (Box 77)
    - Voter's Choice (Box 77)
    - Washington Contributions (Box 77)
    - Weiner, Richard (Box 77)
- Detroit Office Topical Files
  The Detroit office files consist in part of records of Vice Chair Patti Knox. The files also relate to her work as president of the Michigan Federation of Democratic Women.
  - 1960-1968
    - Campaign materials 1964, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Campaign materials 1968, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Concerned Democrats, Michigan Conference of 1967-1968 (Box 78)